One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Okobore Town
‫بلدة أوكوبوري‬
Big Bro! Ma'am!
‫!أخي الكبير، سيدتي‬
Where am I?
‫ما هذا المكان؟‬
My teahouse.
‫إنه محل الشاي الخاص بي‬
Otama!
‫أوتاما-تشان‬
How's your tummy?
‫كيف حال معدتك؟‬
Does it hurt?
‫هل تؤلمك؟‬
I feel better!
‫أشعر بتحسن‬
That worked so fast!
‫كان المفعول سريعًا‬
Five finger grass is quite the wonder drug.
‫أعشاب "تطهير الشر" دواء مدهش‬
Thank you all!
‫شكرًا لكم جميعًا‬
Nin-nin!
‫نين-نين‬
But...
‫...ولكن‬
the poison in your body can't be removed completely.
‫لم يخرج السم من جسدك كليًّا‬
So don't ever drink the river water again, Otama.
‫لذا إيّاكِ الشرب من مياه النهر مجددًا يا أوتاما-تشان‬
Okay, I got it!
‫حسنًا، فهمت‬
Stop making noise, stomach! This is unbecoming of a warrior!
‫كفاكِ قرقرة يا معدتي، هذا ليس من شيمنا‬
Water!
‫ماء‬
River!
‫النهر‬
Otama! Stop right there!
‫أوتاما-تشان، توقفي‬
You must never...!
‫ماء النهر‬
drink the river water again!
‫إيّاكِ أن تشربي منه‬
There, all done. This is only a field dressing though...
‫انتهيت، إنها مجرد إسعافات أولية‬
Yeah. Thank you.
‫أجل، شكرًا لكِ‬
You're so huge.
‫يا لضخامتك‬
Big Mom was way bigger.
‫بيغ مام أضخم منها بكثير‬
Thank you for saving me from the sumo wrestler's attempt at courtship.
‫أشكرك على إنقاذي من مصارع السومو الذي كان يتحرش بي‬
I didn't do anything.
‫لم أفعل شيئًا‬
I forgot to introduce myself.
‫أعتذر عن عدم تقديم نفسي‬
I am your humble servant, Okiku.
‫أنا أدعى أوكيكو‬ ‫سيشا = تعني أنا باليابانية ولا يستخدمها سوى الساموراي الذكور‬
Humble servant?!
‫سيشا؟‬
I can't! No way! I can't!
‫محال، محال، محال‬
Please! Take it away, ma'am!
‫أبعديه من فضلك يا سيدتي‬
I don't even have money for the herbs!
‫لا أملك مالًا لدفع ثمن الأعشاب‬
I can't possibly afford your oshiruko red-bean soup!
‫فما بالك بثمن طبق الأوشيروكو؟‬
You don't have to pay for it.
‫لا داعي لدفع ثمنه‬
No!
‫كلا‬
I can't have it!
‫أعتذر عن تناوله‬
I know both you and Okiku haven't had much to eat either!
‫أعلم أنكِ وأوكيكو-سان لم تأكلا الكثير‬
That's okay. Don't be shy.
‫لا بأس، لا داعي للخجل‬
You've already saved my life and now you're trying to give me food!
‫أنقذتِ حياتي، وها أنتِ الآن تحاولين إطعامي‬
How can I accept this?!
‫كيف لي أن أقبل بهذا؟‬
It's okay.
‫لا بأس‬
No!
‫كلا‬
I said it's okay!
‫أخبرتك لا بأس‬
I'll pay you back for the herbs no matter what!
‫أعدك أنني سأسدد ثمن الأعشاب حتمًا‬
That's enough!
‫طفح الكيل‬
When a woman has served food...
‫حين تقدم المرأة طعامًا‬
"I don't want it."
‫"لا أريد"‬
"Okay."
‫"فهمت"‬
Do you honestly believe she'll just take it back?
‫أتظنين أنها ستقبل بذلك ببساطة؟‬
If you're not gonna eat it...
‫إن لم تتناوليه‬
I'll pour it in the street!
‫فسألقي به‬
No!
‫محال‬
Otama, just eat it!
‫أوتاما-تشان، تناوليه وحسب‬
Miss Otsuru won't take no for an answer.
‫الرفض ممنوع لدى أوتسورو-سان‬
How long are you gonna sit like that?
‫إلى متى ستظلين تنظرين إليه؟‬
You should be happy! Today's your birthday!
‫أنتِ محظوظة، إنه يوم ميلادك‬
Is that true?
‫حقًّا؟‬
That's what I heard.
‫هذا ما سمعته‬
Then, consider it a birthday gift...
‫اقبليه مني بمثابة هدية يوم ميلادك إذًا‬
and eat up.
‫تناوليه‬
It's so yummy!
‫لذيذ‬
This soup is so delicious!
‫!إن هذا لحساءٌ لذيذ‬
Is this your first time having it?!
‫أهذه أول مرة تأكلينه؟‬
Yes!
‫أجل‬
How many days do you think it's been since she last ate anything?!
‫أتعرف كم يومًا مضى على آخر وجبة تناولتها تلك الطفلة؟‬
Despite how hard she works everyday to weave and sell hats,
‫رغم أنها تنسج القبعات كل يوم وتبيعها في السوق‬
there is barely enough money to sustain even a single person!
‫إلا أننا بالكاد نكسب قوت شخص واحد‬
There's even mochi in it!
‫ثمة حلوى موتشي داخله‬
What a fancy treat!
‫!يا لفخارة هذه الوجبة‬
Can't you make some out of your cheek?
‫أليس بمقدورك صنع مثلها من خديك؟‬
You can't fill your stomach with those.
‫لكنها لا تسد جوعي‬
Yum-yum!
‫لذيذ‬
Ma'am! Thank you very much!
‫شكرًا جزيلًا لكِ يا سيدتي‬
I don't think I could ever top such a wonderful birthday!
‫لم أتخيل أن أحظى بيوم ميلاد جميل كهذا‬
I feel bad that my master is missing out!
‫أشعر بالأسى على معلمي‬
Otsuru...
‫أوتسورو-سان‬
This is the greatest day of my life!
‫!هذا أسعد يومٍ في حياتي‬
Children like her are not uncommon...
‫ثمة كثير من الأطفال مثلها‬
here in Wano...
‫في بلاد وانو‬
It's unbelievable that a small child like her doesn't have enough to eat!
‫لا أصدق أنّ أطفالًا بعمرها لا يتسنى لهم تناول الطعام الكافي‬
At least when you're grown up, you can handle the poison.
‫على الأقل بوسع الكبار تناول السم‬
No, you can't!
‫طبعًا لا‬
There's the sea, the mountains, and the forests, so getting food shouldn't be a problem.
‫الحصول على الطعام ليس مسألة صعبة حين تتوفر البحار والجبال والغابات‬
True.
‫أصبت‬
If we only we hadn't ruined them ourselves.
‫إلا إن كان البشر أنفسهم من يلوثونها‬
Damn that Kaido!
‫كايدو اللعين‬
Yeah...
‫أجل‬
You're such sweet young men.
‫أنتما طيبان‬
Oh, yeah! What are your names?
‫بالمناسبة، ما اسمكما؟‬
My name is Zorojuro.
‫أدعى زوروجورو‬
I'm a ronin.
‫أنا رونين‬
I'm Monkey D.–
‫اسمي مونكي دي‬
His name is...
‫اسمه‬
Luffytaro.
‫لوفيتارو‬
R-Right...
‫صـ-صحيح‬
I'm Luffytaro...!
‫أدعى لوفيتارو‬
Verily...?
‫يقينًا‬
You're outsiders, right?
‫أنتما من خارج البلاد، صحيح؟‬
It must've been hard to enter the country.
‫لا بدّ أنّ دخول هذه البلاد كان شاقًّا‬
How could you tell?
‫كيف كشفتنا؟‬
You speak strangely.
‫لهجتكما غريبة‬
Don't worry. I won't tell anybody.
‫لا تقلقا، لن أخبر أحدًا‬
I'm new to this town, too.
‫أنا جديدة على هذه البلدة أيضًا‬
And Okiku has only been working here for a month.
‫وأوكيكو-تشان تعمل هنا منذ شهر فحسب‬
I heard this town is called Okobore.
‫سمعتُ أن اسم هذه البلدة أوكوبوري‬
What kind of name is that?
‫فما قصة اسمها؟‬
It speaks for itself.
‫اسم على مسمى‬
It means "leftovers," and we live off the scraps of the officials the next town over.
‫سكان هذه البلدة يأخذون مخلفات الطعام من بلدة المسؤولين‬
Tama said there is non-poisonous food somewhere.
‫أخبرتني تاما عن مكانٍ يتوفر فيه طعام غير مسموم‬
Look over there.
‫انظر هناك‬
You see the mountain without chimneys?
‫أترى الجبل الذي يخلو من المداخن؟‬
Once upon a time, Oden Castle stood atop it.
‫كانت قلعة أودين تقع في قمته‬
It's already been twenty years.
‫مضت عشرين سنة منذ ذلك الحين‬
Oden... I've heard that word before. But where?
‫أودين؟ سمعت هذا الاسم مسبقًا، ماذا كان يا ترى؟‬
Until some twenty years ago...
‫حتى قبل عشرين سنة‬
the Kozuki clan had long governed the country of Wano.
‫حكمت عشيرة الكوزكي بلاد وانو فترةً طويلة‬
There is a vast farm at the foot of that mountain...
‫تلك المزرعة الفسيحة التي تمتد إلى سفح الجبل‬
that was created by the late Lord Oden
‫شيدها الراحل أودين-ساما‬
and fed the people of Kuri delicious food.
‫من أجل إطعام جميع سكان مقاطعة كوري طعامًا شهيًّا‬
It wasn't meant for Orochi and his cronies to monopolize the country's food supplies.
‫لا يحق لأوروتشي ومن معه احتكار محصول وخيرات هذه البلاد‬
Halcyon Farm...
‫تلك المزرعة المليئة بالخيرات‬
I can hear you!
‫سمعت ذلك‬
So the food there isn't poisonous?
‫أثمة طعام غير مسموم في تلك المزرعة؟‬
Correct.
‫أجل‬
There is safe, delicious food, clean water, and clothes.
‫طعام لذيذ وصحي، وماء عذب، وملابس‬
However, it all belongs to...
‫ولكن كل هذه الخيرات‬
Shogun Orochi!
‫تعود إلى الشوغن أوروتشي‬
On the other side of the shrine gate, there is a town where the officials live.
‫ثمة بلدة على الجانب الآخر من بوابة الضريح المقدس يسكنها المسؤولون‬
To survive, we beg them to sell us rotting food and other things they no longer use.
‫نتوسل إليهم لبيعنا المقتنيات التي لم يعودوا بحاجتها والطعام التالف لنبقى أحياء‬
Okobore, the "leftovers" town...
‫لهذا تُسمى بلدة أوكوبوري؟‬
We get by. At least, we have enough to live.
‫ولكن لا بأس، نحن على قيد الحياة على الأقل‬
What do you think you're doing?! Don't get in my way!
‫ما الذي تفعله أيها اللعين؟ ابتعد عن طريقي‬
I heard what you said, woman!
‫سمعتكِ يا امرأة‬
You were bad-mouthing the shogun!
‫كنتِ تتحدثين بسوء عن الشوغن‬
I can hear six times better than normal humans!
‫حاسة سمعي أقوى من الإنسان العادي بستة أضعاف‬
Batman Bat SMILE Fruit Gifter
‫باتمان غيفتر - مستخدم فاكهة سمايل الخفاش‬
I won't miss a foul word spoken about the Shogun!
‫لن أفوت كلمة سيئة تُقال عن الشوغن‬
So you heard her.
‫فهمت أنك سمعت كلامها‬
Was that really enough reason to try and take her life?
‫ولكن أتراه سببًا وجيهًا لسلب حياتها؟‬
She would've died if you'd hit her.
‫كان سهمك سيقتلها‬
If you live quietly, I'll rarely need to hurt you!
‫ما دمت تعيش بهدوء، فلن أؤذيك‬
But Shogun Orochi...
‫ولكن أوروتشي-ساما‬
isn't one to let treasonous spirits live on!
‫لن يتسامح مع الذين يحملون روح التمرد‬
My arrows!
‫...سهامي‬
He blocked all of them!
‫صدها كلها‬
Who are you?!
‫من تكون؟‬
Someone's been robbing the farm for several weeks.
‫تعرضت المزرعة للسرقة عدة مرات منذ أسابيع‬
We are currently on the lookout for culprits!
‫وما زلنا نبحث عن السارق حتى الآن‬
Perhaps it was you two all along!
‫أيعقل أنكما السارقان؟‬
A one-eyed ronin?!
‫رونين بعين واحدة؟‬
Zorojuro the Slasher
‫زوروجورو تسوجيغيري‬
I've seen him on a wanted poster!
‫لقد رأيته في ملصق المطلوبين‬
Let go of me!
‫دعني وشأني‬
Who are you?!
‫من أنت؟‬
Otama!
‫أوتاما-تشان‬
Help!
‫النجدة‬
Big Bro!
‫أخي الكبير‬
Tama...
‫تاما‬
Gazelleman Gazelle SMILE Fruit Gifter
‫غازلمان غيفتر - مستخدم فاكهة سمايل الغزال‬
Mission accomplished!
‫أُنجزت المهمة‬
Give Tama back!
‫أعد تاما‬
Okiku!
‫أوكيكو-تشان‬
A sword?!
‫سيف؟‬
He runs so fast!
‫يا لسرعته‬
Let go of me!
‫أفلتني‬
Shut up, you little brat!
‫اخرسي أيتها الطفلة اللعينة‬
I'm hopping on, sir lion-dog!
‫دعني أمتطيك يا كوماينو-كن‬
Here, boy!
‫الكلب‬
That woman has a sword!
‫تلك المرأة تحمل سيفًا‬
She said she knew how to use it...
‫قالت أنها تجيد القتال به‬
Though I've never seen her in action...
‫ولكنني لم أرها تستخدمه قط‬
Heel, boy!
‫أيها الكلب‬
Take me with you!
‫خذني معك‬
Look at his arm!
‫ذراعه‬
Wait!
‫مهلًا‬
I'm coming too!
‫سآتي أيضًا‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا‬
Those mongrels!
‫هذان الاثنان‬
Luffytaro! Zorojuro!
‫لوفيتارو-سان، زوروجورو-سان‬
Why are they going after the kid?!
‫ماذا يريدون من تلك الطفلة؟‬
I'm not sure, but we have to get her back!
‫لا أعلم، ولكن علينا إعادتها حالًا‬
Tama!
‫تاما‬
I'm gonna save you!
‫سأنقذك حالًا‬
Big Bro!
‫أخي الكبير‬
Gazelleman! Run like the wind!
‫غازلمان، امضِ بسرعة‬
Roger!
‫عُلم‬
How pathetic!
‫مثيرون للشفقة‬
Dammit!
‫سحقًا‬
They must have planned this kidnapping!
‫واثق أنهما خططا لكل هذا‬
A headliner must've ordered it!
‫لا بدّ أنها أوامر أحد الشينوتشي‬
There is only one place to go in that direction...
‫وثمة بلدة واحدة من هذا الاتجاه‬
The town of officials.
‫إنها بلدة المسؤولين بلا شك‬
A notebook?
‫مذكرة؟‬
There are three headliners in that town.
‫ثمة ثلاثة شينوتشي في تلك البلدة‬
Hawkins.
‫هوكينز‬
Holdem.
‫هولديم‬
Speed.
‫سبيد‬
In addition...
‫وأيضًا‬
there are about thirty warriors with special abilities from those strange artificial fruits.
‫ثمة نحو 30 جندي حصلوا على قدرات مميزة من فواكه اصطناعية غريبة‬
You're no ordinary woman.
‫أنتِ لستِ فتاة عادية‬
Who are you?
‫من تكونين؟‬
This humble servant...
‫...أنا‬
is a samurai.
‫ساموراي‬
Boss Holdem! This is Gazelleman!
‫هولديم-ساما، معك غازلمان‬
I caught the brat who supposedly tamed our baboon!
‫قبضت على الطفلة التي قيل أنها روضت البابون‬
Let me go!
‫أفلتني‬
Well done...
‫أحسنت‬
We'll make good use of her.
‫ستكون مفيدة‬
Bring her here.
‫اجلبها إلي‬
Yes, sir!
‫حاضر‬
Big Bro Luffy!
‫أخي الكبير لوفي‬
This is Bakura, a prosperous town in Wano's Kuri region.
‫هذه بلدة باكورا المزدهرة الواقعة في مقاطعة كوري‬
Restaurant
‫مطعم‬
Damn!
‫سحقًا‬
That pesky ronin!
‫ذلك الرونين اللعين‬
I backed away due to his strangely overpowering spirit,
‫لقد تراجعت بسبب قوة روحه الغامضة‬
but I wanna take Okiku as my wife at any cost!
‫ولكنني سأتزوج أوكيكو مهما كلّف الثمن-بي‬
I have high social status, a good name, and access to safe food supplies.
‫أتمتع بالمكانة العالية والسمعة الحسنة، ولدي مؤن طعام غير مسمومة‬
She'd be crazy to reject me!
‫من الجنون أن ترفضني-بي‬
Stop worrying over trifles, you idiot!
‫كفاك قلقًا أيها الأحمق‬
She's a girl from Okobore Town, right?
‫أليست امرأة من بلدة أوكوبوري؟‬
They're so low-class that Shogun Orochi won't even rule over them...
‫مكانتهم متدنية ولم يعبء أوروتشي-ساما حتى بفرض سيطرته عليهم‬
Whether she loves you or not doesn't matter at all.
‫سواءً كانت تحبك أو تكرهك، فلا يهم‬
You could just force the marriage...
‫تزوجها رغمًا عنها‬
Or you could burn her house down...
‫وإلا احرق منزلها‬
and kill all her relatives so she'll have nowhere else to go.
‫أو اقتل كل أقربائها حتى لا يتبقى لها مكان تعود إليه‬
Isolate her and make her dependent on you!
‫اسلب منها كل خياراتها حتى تكون ملاذها الوحيد‬
You're of the samurai class!
‫أنت من طبقة المحاربين‬
Mouseman Mouse SMILE Fruit Gifter
‫ماوسمان غيفتر - مستخدم فاكهة سمايل الفأر‬
In Wano, our status system is very clear.
‫لدينا تسلسل طبقي واضح في بلاد وانو‬
You're a star of our national sport, so if you give a damn about a lowly person like that,
‫أنت نجم رياضتنا الوطنية، لذا اهتمامك بفتاة من الطبقة الدنيا مثلها‬
you're not setting a good example for others!
‫لن يجعلك قدوةً للآخرين‬
You're right!
‫معك حق-بي‬
Yeah! I can do whatever I want with Okiku!
‫أصبت، يحق لي فعل ما أشاء بأوكيكو‬
Sir Yokozuna... Didn't you like the food?
‫أيها اليوكوزونا، ألم يعجبك الطعام؟‬
That's a tanuki, right?
‫أليس ما تحمله هو راكون؟‬
Yes, this is our long-time pet...
‫أجل، إنه حيواننا الأليف‬
Cook it!
‫اطهوه‬
Tanuki are my favorite food!
‫لحم الراكون هو المفضل لدي‬
Budo
‫فنون قتالية‬
You're finally here...
‫ها قد أتيتِ‬
I see it!
‫أرى البلدة‬
We'll charge right in!
‫سنقتحمها‬
Luffytaro and Zorojuro!
‫لوفيتارو-سان، زوروجورو-سان‬
Beyond that point is Bakura Town! The town of officials and pirates!
‫خلف ذلك المدخل، تقع بلدة باكورا التي يسكنها المسؤولين والقراصنة‬
I cannot guarantee our safety.
‫ليس هنالك ضمانة على حياتنا‬
Are you ready?!
‫أأنتما مستعدان؟‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Is this her?
‫أهذه هي الطفلة؟‬
Poor girl...
‫يا لها من مسكينة‬
She's about to cry.
‫إنها على وشك البكاء‬
I'm not gonna cry!
‫لن أبكي‬
Don't try to act tough!
‫لا تتظاهري بالقوة‬
A Mansion Bakura Town
‫أحد مساكن بلدة باكورا‬
There's a stitch in my side!
‫خاصرتي تؤلمني‬
Shut up! Gazelleman!
‫اخرس يا غازلمان‬
You can go now! Your heavy breathing annoys me!
‫انصرف، لهاثك يزعجني‬
Build up your stamina, you idiot!
‫ارفع معدّل لياقتك‬
I wasn't talking to you!
‫لم أكن أتحدث إليك‬
Stop staring at me like that!
‫توقف عن التحديق إلي هكذا‬
I'm so scared!
‫مخيف‬
Holdem Beast Pirates Headliner Lion SMILE Fruit
‫هولديم شينوتشي في قراصنة الوحوش مستخدم فاكهة سمايل الأسد‬
His tummy's a lion!
‫في بطنه أسد‬
Kamijiro Holdem's Gut
‫كاميجيرو بطن هولديم‬
Oh? You're gonna give me that defiant look?
‫ما بال هذه النظرة العدائية؟‬
What happened?
‫ماذا حدث؟‬
There it is! The lion got him in the nuts!
‫ها قد بدأ، ضربة الخصيتين الخاصة بالأسد‬
But...
‫...ولكن‬
since they share the same body, his groin also belongs to the lion!
‫بما أنهما يتشاركان الجسد نفسه، فذلك العضو يخص الأسد أيضًا‬
Why doesn't he learn?
‫لِمَ لا يتعلم؟‬
Boss Holdem.
‫هولديم-ساما‬
What should we do with this brat?
‫ماذا نفعل بهذه الطفلة؟‬
Boss Holdem!
‫يا هولديم-ساما‬
So your name is Otama.
‫اسمكِ أوتاما، صحيح؟‬
How could a weak little shit like you...
‫أنّى لطفلة شقية ضعيفة مثلك‬
tame a savage baboon?!
‫أن تروض البابون المتوحش؟‬
My men saw you do it!
‫شاهدك رجالي وأنتِ تروضينه‬
Don't pretend like you don't know!
‫لا تتظاهري بالجهل‬
You must have a genuine devil fruit power.
‫إنها قدرة فاكهة شيطان حقيقية حتمًا‬
Come on...
‫هيا‬
Spit it out!
‫تحدثي‬
Otama!
‫أوتاما، قدرتك تجذب انتباه أعدائك حتى‬
You must never be seen using it!
‫إيّاكِ واستخدامها أمام الآخرين‬
I-It's just...
‫ا-الأمر وما فيه‬
animals...
‫أنّ الحيوانات‬
tend to like me.
‫تحبني لا أكثر‬
I see!
‫فهمت‬
That's all it was!
‫هكذا هو الأمر إذًا‬
Yes, that's right.
‫أجل‬
Do you think I'm a fool?!
‫هل تستغفليني؟‬
You damn brat!
‫أيتها الطفلة الشقية‬
"She tore off part of her cheek." That's what they told me.
‫سمعت أنكِ تأخذين قطعة من خدك‬
If you're not gonna tell me...
‫إن رفضتِ إخباري‬
I'll try that myself.
‫فسأتحقق بنفسي‬
Hey, bring me some pincers!
‫أنت، أحضر لي كمّاشة‬
Yes, sir!
‫حاضر‬
Not that one! The bigger one!
‫ليست تلك، بل الكبيرة‬
Big Bro Luffy...
‫...أخي الكبير لوفي‬
Help! Big Bro Luffy!
‫النجدة يا أخي الكبير لوفي‬
Tama!
‫تاما‬
Stop right there! Don't you value your lives?!
‫توقفوا، ألا تهمكم حياتكم؟‬
Invaders!
‫إنهم دخلاء‬
Bakura Town is just past them!
‫بلدة باكورا خلفهم‬
Luffy! We don't have time to fight those weaklings!
‫لوفي، لا وقت لدينا لقتال هؤلاء الضعفاء‬
I know!
‫أعلم‬
Just keep charging, boy!
‫انقضّ عليهم أيها الكلب‬
Captain!
‫قبطان‬
We have a problem!
‫مصيبة‬
What? Why are you so worked up?
‫ماذا؟ ما كل هذه الجلبة؟‬
It's Straw Hat and Roronoa!
‫إنهما قبعة القش ورورونوا‬
Straw Hat is in Wano?! So... he's finally here...
‫قبعة القش-يا في بلاد وانو؟‬
Straw Hat and Roronoa are storming Bakura Town!
‫اقتحم قبعة القش ورورونوا بلدة باكورا‬
Hey, wait! That's gonna cause nothing but trouble!
‫مهلًا، ليس هذا ما خططنا له‬
Pretty much...
‫صحيح‬
Captain?
‫قبطان؟‬
Let's go stop those idiots!
‫لنذهب لردع هذين الأحمقين‬
Aye aye, Captain!
‫حاضر يا قبطان‬
Don't do it...
‫لا تفعل هذا‬
I'll stop as soon as you show me your ability.
‫أريني قدرتك إن لم ترغبي مني أن أفعلها بنفسي‬
Tama!
‫تاما‬
Did you do something?!
‫أفعلت شيئًا؟‬
That was haki!
‫هاكي‬
Haki?
‫هاكي؟‬
Conqueror's haki.
‫الهاكي الملكي‬